all-freeware.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy FreeDownload64.Com - Software Programs - Best Free Software Downloads Center

**Free Download 64 values Your privacy.**

**Personal Information**   
Free Download 64 collects personal information about our users during registration, from our use of "cookie" technology as you use the service. 

Free Download 64 uses reasonable precautions to keep any personal information disclosed to us secure and we never disclose such information to third parties without your express permission. We only ever use personal information for the exact purpose we stated when you gave it to us. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties which receive the information. FreeDownload64.com also links to other sites. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.

**Aggregated Information**   
We also collect aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. Such information enables us to better tailor our content to visitors' needs and to help our advertisers better understand the demographics of our audience. Because FreeDownload64.com derives its revenue mainly from advertising, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential to keeping our service free to users. 

**Third Party Advertising, Cookies**   
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you, on your behalf, by our advertising partners. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or any other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser, but it will not collect any personally identifiable information about you. 

**Contact Free Download 64**   
Please contact us at for more information about our privacy policy if required.
